Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive!
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me!
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you!
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Everyone!
We found Dalton over here!
What? Yeah!
Fantastic!
We're coming!
Dalton!
Who's Dalton?
This is horrible I can't feel a heartbeat.
I've prepared this extra nutritious and
fortifying meal just for you so we can
get a healthy smile back on that beautiful
face of yours thank you Sanji of course
Although you're as heartbreakingly
gorgeous as ever in spite of your painful
ordeal Hey you I don't recall you asking
for permission to use my kitchen Madam,
I made a dish for you as well.
It's supposed to make you look years...
I'm not a madam.
I'm a swinging single
still in the prime of you.
Don't forget it.
Not a day over 139, right? Dr.
Lee, save me from this loaded tape!
Wait, hold on, come back!
What are you doing? Luffy?
This guy's gonna join
us and be our friend!
Really? Great!
I didn't say I was going to do that!
Sure you did!
No, I didn't!
Be quiet, both of you!
Friend, huh?
If he only knew what friend means to
someone who's been through what Chopper has.
Poor guy.
When Chopper was out there on his own,
there was only one human that
he ever really opened up to.
That man's name was Dr. Hiriluk.
He was a crazy quack, but he named
Chopper and called him his son.
Hey, you! Stop!
Where'd he go?
He beats me, and he disappeared.
Crazy quack!
We've got to get him!
Those are Lord Waple's
orders. Now move out! Right!
You can't go on like this.
We have to call a doctor.
We can't.
There are no doctors left to call.
Except for the 20 mds who belong to Wapol.
If we have to beg Wapol on our knees
for help then that's what we have to do.
I'll go get them.
You don't need waple's charity.
I'll examine him. Here, look!
No, I'm fine.
It's just a cold.
Besides, the last bunch of patients you
treated ended up getting a whole lot worse.
Now, there's no need to
be shy with your doctor.
I just developed a wonderful
new old-purpose drug yesterday.
You're a lucky man.
Now, shut up.
Oh, that's not the kind
of gun you think it is.
It's a tranquilizer gun for
patients with severe pain.
I'm going to get the soldiers.
Please go if you want money I'll be glad
to pay I don't take
money from sick people.
I just want to help you don't do
it please I'm too young to die.
Huh okay I gotta admit
I wasn't expecting that
I must have made a mistake
with the ingredients.
somehow.
Guess I shouldn't have used frog extract.
Uh, sorry there. My mistake.
Pyrrha, look!
Are you in there?
Hold it!
Are you happy now? Quack!
The Dr.
Hunt has reached its final stage.
I hear you and I are the only
ones left in the country.
Wapol has his hunters desperately
looking for us everywhere.
And even if they weren't, you'd
already be a pariah in this country.
Since you're the worst quack of them all.
I'm not going to get caught
by some fool doctor hunt.
And one day I'll end up saving
this country with medical science.
Yeah, right.
I think you mean destroy this country.
Look, there are people on the bridge.
See you around, quack.
Not if I see you first,
you thieving sawbones.
Those tin soldiers
aren't gonna capture me.
I'm gonna go on helping
the sick and the injured.
Looks like you've been shot.
We need to stop the bleeding
right away or you're dead.
Don't worry.
I'll save you.
It's a Yeti! Shoot it!
Actually, you're pretty lucky,
because I just created an ointment three
days ago that even works on broken bones.
We can't let that Blue
Moose Yeti get away, man!
Kill him before he kills us!
Shoot him down!
Just what are you, anyway?
You don't look like a human being.
You must be that Yeti everyone
is talking about in the village.
Yeah! We got him!
It wasn't enough. Finish him!
How dare you?
Who do you think you're
dealing with, creature?
Hey, wait!
I promise I'm not gonna shoot you, see?
My name is Hiriluk, Dr. Hiriluk!
And I wanna help you!
It's not a good thing.
It's a pretty good thing.
You'll have to go to the next one.
This is just a good thing.
Well, I wonder if I am doing something.
I'm going to go.
That was the first encounter
between Chopper and Dr. Hiriluk.
So, what happened next?
Between Chopper and Dr. Hiriluk?
Wait, you can talk?
Why have you kept silent?
I thought you'd hate me if I talked.
When I talked to humans the
other day, they shot at me.
You see, people think
I'm a freak for that.
So you can talk, so what?
Even children learn to talk.
I don't see what's damn special about it.
Ah!
Run, Chopper!
Aw, I thought for sure that would work.
Hey, Chopper, are you okay?
Eh?
Well, at least your head was
bandaged to begin with, right?
Hey, did you call me Chopper?
That's your new name, Tony.
Tony Chopper.
I picked it because I
thought you'd look like you
could chop down a tree with
those antlers of yours.
Cool name, huh?
Anyway, that's what I'm going to call you.
Sir.
Now listen up, Chopper.
Always pay close attention
to your patient's
symptoms and give them proper treatment.
That's the way to save a person's life.
Let's go.
There are sick people who need my help.
Get out of here, you crazy clown!
I thought lizard eyeballs would work!
Don't ever come back! Girls!
It's Waffle's guards! Run!
Chopper, it's time to use the decoy plant!
The wood plant?
Good luck, pal!
You almost got me killed,
you maniac! So what?
You already cheated death once,
you clumsy Pluto's caribou?
That's reindeer and don't call me Pluto!
Hey!
Doctor, that's the first time
I've ever fought with anyone.
I can believe that.
You have to have an opponent to fight.
So is it your first time for this as well?
That's for you. A gift.
As a memento of our making up.
Gift?
Making up?
You know, Chopper, it sometimes
feels that things are pretty rough.
But try not to hold a grudge
against us humans, okay?
This country is sick right now.
The people and the king both suffer
from a terrible sickness of the heart.
The conventional wisdom has it that
there is no way to cure a sick country.
But that's wrong.
Once my invention has been perfected,
this country will be as good as saved.
You see, there used to be a master thief
who lived in a country in the far west.
He had a serious heart condition.
He went to the greatest doctors he
could find to receive treatment.
But no one was able to cure him.
They told him he was going to die.
Frustrated and depressed, he
passed by a certain mountain.
There he saw something
he had never seen before.
Blossoms!
He saw cherry blossoms
all over the mountainside.
And then he went to see another doctor and
got the shock of his
life because he was told,
you're perfectly healthy.
Huh?
He was cured. It was a
miracle. Don't you see?
But it also makes perfect
sense medically speaking.
By changing his emotional state,
he was able to change his
physical state somehow too.
And if that's true, there's no disease
in this world that can't be cured.
Let them laugh at me.
My medical skills will
save this country yet.
And that's why I raised
this skull and cross bones.
As a challenge to all the
diseases of the world.
This symbolizes my belief
that nothing is impossible.
I will save this country
with my doctor's skills.
By raising this flag, I vow to
fight just like the pirates do.
Hey, reindeer!
Join us and be our friend!
Booty!
I don't be a pirate!
Doctor, what are pirates? Pirates?
They're dashing
swashbucklers of the sea with
great strength and the eyesight of eagles.
Their voices echo like rolling thunder.
Hey, you're really a pirate? Huh?
Well, yeah, of course I am.
It's like I've been saying all along.
We do all kinds of fun stuff,
like fishing and singing.
Huh?
Pirates sing?
Sure we do.
And sometimes we dance, too.
You call that being a pirate?
Of course.
And we go on adventures. You really do?
Pirates really do go on adventures?
Yeah, you bet we do.
Pirates risk their lives
to go on adventures.
And you meet the most amazing people.
It's great to be a pirate.
The most amazing people sail the seas.
Chopper, someday you've got to go to sea.
If you do,
you'll realize just how
small your problems really
are in comparison to the
vastness of the oceans.
The island you were born on is
like this compared to the world.
Really?
No, it's smaller, like this.
Your destiny lies beyond that shining sea.
The good times passed in
the twinkling of an eye.
and then
it finally came time to say farewell.
as it always does in the end?
it's taken a year but your
treatment is finally complete.
your injuries are healed chopper.
Yeah, thank you, Doctor.
Well then, take care.
On your way, have a nice life.
I'm busy with my research.
So hit the bricks.
I'm no longer under any
obligation to care for you.
Doctor, I swear I won't cause you any
trouble if you'll just let me stay with you.
I'll rub your shoulders every day.
I'll make you tea and clean the house.
Please let me stay.
I don't have any friends.
I don't have anywhere to go.
Doctor!
Please!
Can you hear me?
Doctor!
Chopper!
I hurt my head.
I fell.
I'm injured.
Take a look!
But why, Doctor?
Go!
Go to sea if you like!
Go anywhere you want!
Just don't come back!
Ah!
Forgive me, Chopper!
I'm dying.
Yes you are tell me the truth
how many days do i have left?
Excuse me this isn't a charity!
Ward you don't have the
money to pay my fee?
Tell me!
You can't kill a person with
a tranquilizer gun you know.
All right, I'll tell you.
Ten days from now, you'll
die, so now you know.
Ten?
That'll be enough.
In two days, my research will be done.
Now completed, after failing for 30 years,
I will make cherry blossoms
bloom in this country.
You mean, you've wasted 30 years
researching freaking cherry blossoms?
That's what your big project has been?
The same cherry blossoms you think saved
your life back when you
were a master thief?
That's right. What?
Damn, you idiot.
This is a winter island where
it's bitter cold year-round.
No cherry blossom will ever bloom here.
No.
I was nothing but a worthless criminal.
On the very brink of death,
but those flowers saved my life
and transformed my existence.
Every human being in
this world can be saved.
And I'm going to prove it right here
in Drum, the land where I was born.
Right.
You do realize that what
you're saying has no basis
in medical science or any
other field of science,
and if you do get them to bloom,
there's no medicinal use.
Here, look.
Chopper, you and I are alike.
So before I die, I'll at least teach you
that nothing is impossible in this world.
and that you can do anything if you try.
However, the story of these two outcasts
doesn't have a happy fairy tale ending.
Get away from me!
Come back!
That scent. Huh?
Papa.
When he found out Hiriluk
only had 10 days to live,
Chopper got very upset,
as you might imagine.
It was only natural.
But then he decided to take
action the only way he knew how.
I'm dying.
I promise you, I will make
cherry blossoms bloom!
This symbolizes my belief
that nothing is impossible!
I'll fight like pirates!
Tell me, why have so many
guards been missing lately?
Well, the 20MDs have them
out picking mushrooms.
Mushrooms? Yes, sir.
The doctors think there's some kind
of mushroom that can cure anything,
so they've got the other
guards out looking for it.
Mushroom?
You idiot!
They'll spot us!
Doctor, did you hear what they said?
I promise I'm not going to shoot you, see?
Go where you want, but don't come back!
I did a terrible thing to you.
But at least you'll
see my cherry blossoms!
They'll be my last great work.
Okay, one more time!
Dammit, I'm running out of time.
I've gotta hurry.
Nothing is impossible for a
man who raises the pirate flag.
Isn't that what I told you, huh?
I'll keep on fighting.
Just like the pirates.
I found it, the amyudaki mushroom.
That's it!
How do I get across?
Damn it!
Doctor, I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I lost one
of your precious books.
Good Lord, what happened to you?
Mushroom.
Medicine.
Is that for me?
An amyadaki mushroom?
Please, Liv.
Please, doctor.
I want to help people like you.
Please teach me to be a doctor, okay?
I'll fight and I won't
give up, just like pirates.
Chumper, I...
You think a reindeer can?
Of course, yes.
Yes.
You'll be a wonderful doctor.
Doctor, I can't breathe.
I know you'll be a wonderful doctor.
Because you have such a kind heart.
Chess!
Kuromariimo!
Is hunting the doctors
proceeding according to my plan?
Yes, nearly all the doctors
have been exiled, sir.
Nearly all?
There are two that still elude us, sire.
That old crone, Dr. Kureha.
And that crazy quack.
Here you look.
What did you say?
Oh, I just had a great idea.
Send a notice to the people.
Tell them that the 20 MDs
have all fallen gravely ill.
How's the mushroom soup? Good?
Ah, this reeks!
No living creature could eat this soup.
Sorry.
Hey, don't worry about it.
Good medicine never tastes good, you know.
That just means it's working.
Thanks for the soup, Chopper.
What's that?
I've done it.
I've finally done it.
This is it.
This reaction.
I've been waiting 30 years for this.
i've done it chopper my
research is a success
i was right all along see that see that
i can't do it i can make cherry
blossoms bloom on this winter island
I'm going out, but you stay
put and rest Okay See you later
Doctor was happy
Wow, I cured a human's disease
You're going to become a great
doctor I'll make sure of it
you realize this entire country is
a madhouse right now yeah i noticed
have you heard about the 20 mds falling
ill what a crock so what brings you
here today i have a favor to ask i
refuse anything else i haven't even
asked it yet so what is this dust
supposed to be that dust is 30 years of my
life it's the discovery i've been
searching for it'll treat this country's
sickness and it'll cure it you just
wasted 30 years of your life nicely
done anyway why are you showing it to
me i wasn't able to make enough dust
there's no time i want you to make
cherry blossoms bloom for me nonsense
why should i waste my finished i want
you to teach chopper about medicine
he wants to be a doctor more than
anything are you mad he may be a reindeer
and a freak but i know he'll make a
great doctor he's a good person with
a kind heart he risked his life to
make medicine for me please help him
become a doctor you've sure got a lot
of nerve you quack why should I take
care of your half-baked research and
your weird bet you know me I'm not
the type to get all sentimental just
because someone has a short time to
live now get out
of my tree yeah I
know we've known each other a long time
goodbye this doesn't seem
like you here look to
give up so easily I'm almost out
of time no No, he couldn't, I mean.
What do you mean?
The 20MDs are ill?
Who will treat the country's sick people?
At least give us medicine.
It's no good talking to us.
We're just telling you.
Everyone get out of my way!
I can't move it!
That gun's insane.
Head for the ropeway, then the castle.
Where's that damn fool hero look?
For crying out loud,
you don't have to hide.
I know all about you.
Now, where'd that quack run off to?
Damn it, talk!
D-Doctor got better, so he went
into town. That's all. Better?
He can't get better.
His condition can't be cured by any
treatment known to modern medical science.
That's not true!
Look at this.
He's all better now, because
I gave him this to eat.
It can't be.
This is an all-purpose
medicine, so he's fine now.
He said he felt like
he was full of energy.
Doctor said he was going
to teach me to do it!
What was that?
You stupid fool!
Don't you know?
That mushroom!
It's poison.
Once you eat it, you're
dead in half a day.
That's why that idiot came to me.
That can't be true.
I checked in one of Doctor's books.
Though I guess I lost the book somehow.
It can defeat all diseases.
I raised this flag as a challenge
to all the diseases of the world.
That's right.
There was a skull next to the
picture of the Amiodaki mushroom.
And Doctor said he got better.
There's no way he'll die.
You're lying to me.
Stop dawdling!
Hurry it up!
I haven't got any time left to waste!
He was touched by the
kindness in your heart.
The skull in that book
means poison, understand?
No, remember it.
There is no known medicine in this
world that can work for all diseases.
That's why doctors exist. But I...
Listen, you can't save
people with just kindness.
If you really want to save them,
you need medical skills and
the training to use them.
Without that you can't save anyone
You poor fool.
Lord Wapol, Hiriluk is
headed towards the castle.
It worked!
Fool!
Is he serious? Why?
What for?
He'll never return to this house.
I guess he chose the
castle to be his tomb.
I demand that you take me to the patients.
I've come to save the 20 MDs.
What?
You idiot!
Don't you get it yet?
It was a trap!
The 20 MDs are fine, as you can see!
The only life in danger
here is yours, Dr. Hiriluk!
Why did he come here?
Guards! Ready!
So that was it.
God.
And none of them are sick.
I was afraid this was a national crisis,
but no, luckily it was just a trick.
Ha!
If it really was a national crisis,
I wouldn't want someone like you.
Ignore his babbling!
Execute him!
Save your bullets.
You don't have what it takes
to kill someone like me.
Huh?
Hey, when do you think a person dies?
When a bullet from a pistol
pierces his heart? No.
When he's attacked by an
incurable disease? No.
When he eats a soup of deadly
poisonous mushrooms? No!
A man dies when people forget him.
Even if I should disappear right
now, my dream will come true.
And when it does, the citizen's sickness
of the heart will be cured as well.
You're crying?
Why, Dalton?
Is that true for a country?
Yeah, if the will to do it is passed on.
Come on, Dalton!
Why are you crying?
Very shortly, a monster will be coming.
He's my son.
Please, don't hurt him.
Don't worry, Chopper.
Your mushroom won't kill me.
I've had a marvelous life!
Goodbye, Quack.
Thank you, Chopper!
He blew himself off!
What an idiot!
Oh, crap! It's nothing!
It's a monster!
Shoot him!
Shoot him! Stop!
Leave!
Leave here at once!
If you can't even defeat me,
you can't possibly defeat them!
I apologize for those who had the
nerve to laugh at Hyruleuk's death.
Without enough strength,
you'd only die in vain.
Don't waste your life.
Don't sacrifice it for this country.
Please.
Huh?
You let him get away!
Just shut your mouth!
The only man who cared
enough to try to cure
this sick country has just
died while you laughed!
Even while everyone else
just gave up in despair,
this kind doctor attempted to
save us all and died for it!
So what if someone like that dies?
I've seen the path this
country should take.
It should just die out!
As long as we stay here,
it can't be rebuilt, because
even if medical care progresses,
even if medical research goes on,
there is no medicine that can cure fools!
I let you have your say, and all
you've done is make me angry!
Please!
Please teach me how to be a doctor!
You've got to teach me
how to become a doctor.
You've got to.
I'll become the all-purpose medicine.
I'll become a doctor
who can cure anything.
You'll see.
I'll even cure a country.
I'll do anything you ask of me,
but I've got to become a doctor.
Because I know there's no disease, no
illness in this world that can't be cured.
Call me Dr.
Rain from now on.
I won't die.
I'll carry on.
His will.
So for the six years since then, Chopper's
been studying medicine under you. Yeah.
I taught him everything I know.
He's been a good student.
Dr. Ean! Dr. Ean!
Dr. Ean! There's trouble!
Waffle is back!
Is he?
It's him!
The guy with the annoying mouth!
I have returned, finally!
Now, at long last, we
shall restore Drum Kingdom!
Waffle, sir, look!
On top of the castle!
Why is that strange flag
flying? It's an outrage!
Where's the flag of the Drum Kingdom?
That old thing, I burned it!
Well, Kureha, the last survivor of
our Doctor Hunt, get out of my castle!
This castle is no longer yours, Wapol!
It saw enough corruption and
misery during your reign!
Leave!
Not just here, the country too!
Drum Kingdom has already died out, moron!
What's that?
Wait!
This guy is mine!